when I was little I had to get a real
woman a real girl and we would go to the
woods and I would try and take her top
off for
[Applause]
[Music]
real
so here's the story with the show really
simple just a bunch of funny people are
all telling true stories uh I'm really
excited to have this guy he's one of the
funniest men in America Mr Tom Papa
everybody let him
here I have uh a lot of women in my life
I've always had a lot of women in my
life I was raised with girls uh my mom
was a girl uh my grandmother was a girl
I uh I married a girl and uh now I've
made my own girls I have my own girls
that I've made yeah I made them and
um people always ask me things like do
you think they'll end up working at a
huh and uh yeah
[Laughter]
maybe
I mean they're little now all I can go
by is their gymnastic moves and they're
they got that covered they're good with
that then it's just going to come down
to desire how badly do they want
it they can make their dreams come true
people always ask me like are you
worried about them now like are you
worried about kids I can't believe like
with phones are you worried that these
kids have these phones and I would hate
raising children now with these phones
aren't you terrified of what they're
going to do with these phones no I'm not
worried about them at all they're going
to handle it they'll be fine I'm not
worried about what it's going to do to
them I'm worried about what it's doing
to me it's making me into a nosy borish
douchebag I am spying on my own
creatures I made these people and I'm
spying on them it's so douchy it's such
an awful way to live I don't care what
they do why am I invading and spying on
what you know I back off you care that
your son is on boobs.com
really really your little guys in there
boobs big boobs
Doc is that really bad when I was little
I had to get a real woman a real girl
and we would go to the woods and I would
try and take her top off for
real cuz there was no dot anything and
we would just do it until finally she
would take her top off and she was happy
and I was happy and our parents didn't
know about it they weren't spying
through our they weren't going
through my text they weren't doing any
of that so who cares just back off let
them do what they're going to do this is
the way I've always wanted to do it they
you have tools it's a tool they have a
tool this is their tool to get laid
everyone has a tool in their ERA this is
their tool you want to get laid you got
to learn to use this
tool I needed a car I needed a godamn
damn car I needed to get in a car and
drive around and look for women that was
my tool and I knew that at a young age
and I bought a car 2 years before I was
able to
drive I busted my ass I went out and
bust tables in a shitty little
restaurant called The Orchards in a
Hilton hotel I would just put on a green
bow tie and I would walk at 4:00 in the
morning down to the school wait for my
friend to pick me up cuz he had a car
already and I would just sit there and
shiver and he would come and pick me up
and he was the king he was the king but
I bited my time cuz I knew you're not
going to be the king for long I might be
in a green bow tie now but I will be
king in two goddamn
years and I just kept working I didn't
get respect I got my ass kicked I just
sitting there with a bow tie people
would just be like get over here more
water boy more rolls boy and I would
just lick him and put him in the
basket I was like yeah I may have a
green bow tie but I'm a badass
underneath
it and I saved up and I got $1,600
$1,600 and I called my uh Uncle Uncle Al
he ran a junkyard and uh we called him
Uncle Al all the kids pal cuz he always
had weed always had a lot of weed yeah
still does still does and he's he's
still our pal and I said Uncle Al I got
$1,600 he said I got a car for you I got
a car for you I used1 19 82 Toyota
Corolla I said that sounds great what
color is it he said baby
orange sold I'll take it and I put him
in my in my garage and I couldn't drive
it for two years I just pet it I would
pet it and talk to it and just wait for
the day when I was able to go out and
find girls and when I turned 17 it was
time to hunt I would it was like a
hunting dog I would just give it a scent
I found a scrunchie on the in the park
smell it boy smell
it and we Cruis around and it worked we
got girls we got girls and baby
orange that was how powerful having a
car was and that's when I met Heidi I
met this beautiful girl she became my
girlfriend she was gorgeous she was six
feet tall six feet tall no no no it
wasn't the big scary goonish 6 feet tall
it wasn't like hey
Tom I don't think I can fit in baby
orange no this was like long legs
athletic gorgeous girl and we would just
that was it we just got in baby
orange we went everywhere to the beach
to the mountains just having sex
everywhere we went we were like sexual
athletes just in between those giant
long legs and my parents didn't know
about it cuz they couldn't go
through my text cuz it didn't exist it
didn't exist I learned everything from
her I learned how I learned how to
please a woman orally from because
you're 17 stamina you they don't make a
drug that could make me that strong
right now they don't it does not exist
if you're 17 you are like you're like a
lion you're just so but you're not good
you're not good it's not going to last
long it's going to be and just it's
going to be over that's where you learn
to please a woman another way and if you
have a man in your life that pleases you
orally it's not cuz he cares about you
it's cuz he doesn't last very
long he needs different skills and we
never got caught we never got caught we
just getting laid for years I would
literally drive my car home for curfew
go to bed say good night to everyone
wait for them to sleep and around
midnight I'd open my window I'd go out
on the garage roof I would hang on the
gutter I'd have my little legs down
until I felt the the banister below me
then I get on that all those moves took
like a half hour each one of them I was
do I hear anything do I hear anything
and then drop and then I push baby
orange into the street and we would just
cruise down no and then pop it into gear
wi go up to hadi's House Park in her
bushes and she lived like way down here
and her parents were way up there and I
would just climbing her window and we'd
have sex every single night and baby
Shar just stood there waiting for me and
I would go back and I'd climb back in
and every night I never got caught never
got caught until one night one night in
the middle of these long legs I'm doing
what I was taught to do in an oral
Manner and the door opened the door
opened and a light of just shown on my
17-year-old white ass it was her father
it was her father and this is what he
says Tom it's time to go home
now that was it and Clos the door and
close the I was freaked out I'm like
what do I do do I just put my clothes on
and go out the front door he knows I'm
here do I have to climb out the window I
think I'm I'll go out the window he's
probably's he acted so cool I'm like he
probably has an axe in the
hallway let me just go out the window so
I went out the window and I love this
girl she was my girlfriend so I had to
come back the next day and confront the
father and apologize cuz I loved her I
wanted to be with her and I actually got
in my car it was a Sunday and I drove up
to her house to apologize to the father
of this girl I had such stronger
character at
17 than I have right now if that
happened right now I'd never see this
girl
again I would just get in baby
orange and just go leave to another
state but I was like no I'm going to do
it I'm going to sit down I'm going to
I'm just going to apologize I remember
he was watching tennis he was watching
tennis he didn't even look up I was like
I'm really really sorry I didn't mean to
be here in here I know it was late I
should I shouldn't have been in here
have voice all cracking I didn't say
exactly what I was doing cuz I didn't
know what he saw I don't want be like I
really shouldn't have been going down on
her but I don't last that
long so I just went with the it's late I
was just it was really late and this is
what he says he goes who you kids and
kept watching
tennis I was like this is the greatest
man alive
forget Gandhi this guy is at peace this
guy is centered this guy is just one
with the universe I'm like I'm going to
be this guy when I get older this is the
father that I am going to be I'm going
to be so chill and so Zen I'm going to
be exactly like this guy cuz he didn't
kill me and I'm going to be this guy and
uh I fast forward I've made my own
people I've made my own people I have a
daughter and my wife wife just tells me
thank you and my wife tells me just
sitting there chopping vegetables she
just lets it be known just kind of out
the side of her mouth just like it's
nothing you know there's a boy texting
your
daughter
woo that would have been the Zen
response
woo but I didn't I just yelled out get
me her
phone
no Zen no nothing I don't even use I
don't curse a lot in my life ever and
now in front of my little daughter and
cats and everybody else I just blurred
out in my own kitchen get me her
phone and this is how awful this is why
I feel so nosy and shitty I get her
phone and I'm like all right I'm gonna
now let's see what this is about where
is it I know her code I can use this
yeah oh here he is here he is the little
bird let's see what he's doing with
our
daughter first text is like what are you
going to be for Halloween I'm thinking
of Batman ha haa she's like oh I might
be snow white LOL rainbow rainbow
unicorn what's your favorite candy kiit
at bars me too Pizza
Pizza little thing dancing I can't wait
for the parade me need either Hank Hank
Han hearts hearts hearts smiley
face what a piece of I
am total piece of
so I'm off I'm not going to uh go
through her phone
anymore I will take a drill and bolt her
window shut
but I'm going to stay off her phone
thank you guys so
[Music]
[Applause]
much